Tracy Nguyen

Garden Grove, CA 92843 tracynguyen121@gmail.com tracyhnguyen.github.io

An open minded and reliable junior whose creativity motivates her to be a diligent, hard worker. Her many experiences and volunteer service allows her to quickly adapt to new situations as her strong knowledge of technology and computer assists her in any obstacle she faces.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 | La Quinta High School | GPA: 3.84

 Exploring Computer Science, AP Computer Science Principles, AP Computer Science A

- Viet 2, Viet 3, Viet 4 Honors
- English 1 Honors, English 2 Honors, AP English Language and Composition

SKILLS & KNOWLEDGE

Bilingual

• Vietnamese & English

Interpersonal Skills

• Communication, collaboration, problem solving, active listener • Google: Docs, Slides, Sheets, Forms,

Computer Science

• Coding: HTML, CSS, Scratch, Python, Java

Technology/Digital Platforms

- Devices: Laptop, Computer, Smartphones;
 Windows & Apple/Mac
- Google: Docs, Slides, Sheets, Forms Drawings, Sites, Calendar
- Social Media: Facebook, Instagram

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2017 | National Junior Honor Society (45+ service hours completed)

- Worked in a group of 35 other members in running school fundraiser events
- Complete service inside/outside of school

2019 - 2020 | Interact Club Publicist and Event Coordinator (34+ service hours completed)

- Created promotional flyers for events/meetings and informational slides for meetings
- Managed the club's social medias: Facebook Page and Group, Instagram, created and managed the club website
- Attended and spoke at meetings within other students, members, and adults
- Provided community service opportunities and organized transportation for members (2 events a month)

PROJECTS

January 2019 - March 2020 | Doubles Badminton Tournament

- Managed La Quinta HS's first Doubles Badminton Tournament open to all students after Interact Advisor and President worked with school Admin on spearheading the event
 - o Organized 86 teams (172 participants) into games for each round, managed Winners/Losers Bracket
 - Checked in/out teams, recorded scores, refereed matches at every game (3 days a week; 9 games a day)

May 2020 - June 2020 | Personal Website

- Coded the website on my own using HTML and CSS as a digital portfolio
- Link: <u>tracyhnguyen.github.io</u>

VOLUNTEERING

2010 - Current | Altar Server at La Vang Church (700+ service hours completed)

• Work in a group of 7 for 1.5 hours almost every Sunday to help during Mass

2018 - Current | Viet Faith Formation at St. Barbara (130+ service hours completed)

• Teacher's Assistant/teach lesson plans; manages the first grade class for an 1.5 hours every Saturday

2018 - Current | California Scholarship Federation (8+ service hours completed)

• Active member; tutored high school peers after school in the library, assisted teachers